Let's talk about a safety technique for ice fishing, and that involves what are called ice creepers.
When I got to the lake this morning I immediately looked around and said, "This looks like a skating rink.
This ice is slick.
If I walk around with just my regular boots carrying all my gear, be it the auger or my tackle, there's a good chance that I'm going to slip, I'm going to hurt myself, maybe break some equipment."
So I always carry ice creepers with me.
There's a couple different styles.
This one is simply a more of an elastic strap that fits around your boot, and it hooks back to here.
Again, these sit on the bottom of your boot so that they come in contact with the ice and give you some stability.
There's another type which simply has a clip and a strap, and all you do is carefully put that over.
Make sure that the bottom of it is facing downward and then you just cinch it up as tight as you can, again making certain, as you can see, that it's on the bottom of your boot.
Then when you walk, this will give you the stability that you need.
You don't slip, it grips very, very well, and it will keep you from getting injured or from damaging your equipment.